DUSAN DIVAC

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

PROFILE

Accomplished full stack developer with strong experience in the development of web applications like SaaS, CRM, eCommerce, market places, FinTech platforms, etc based on JavaScript and PHP.

Have solid idea & knowledge of software development methodologies while being a proficient DevOps engineer who is familiar with the implementation of CI/CD based on Github/BB pipelines, Jenkins, Docker, etc.

CONTACT

A: Branislava Nušića 216, Leštane, Serbia L: linkedin.com/in/dusan-divac E: dusan.divac.d2@gmail.com

SKILLS

1. Front-end development

- React, NextJS, Gatsby, React Native
- Vue, Nuxt, Vuetify, Quasar
- Angular, AngularJS, Angular Material UI, Kendo UI, Ionic
- Tailwind, Boostrap, Bulma
- HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Less, jQuery

2. Back-end development

- Node.js, Express.js, Loopback.io, NestJS
- Laravel, Symfony
- MongoDB, MySQL,
 PostgreSQL, Amazon
 DynamoDB

3. DevOps

- CI/CD
- TDD
- Docker
- GitLab, Bitbucket Pipelines

EXPERIENCE

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Self-Employed | Aug 2021 - Present

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

EVERDRIN | May 2018 - Sept 2021

- Built admin panel by Vue.js and Laravel.
- Performed code reviews on team members in order to enforce high-quality code for MERN.
- Created a web application for a financial company
- Worked as lead developer for a project with a Node back-end and React front-end that was deployed to AWS.
- Developed a CRM system to manage a tire warehouse using the JavaScript framework, Vue.js.
- Architected and developed an integration solution based on AWS Lambda, API Gateway, Cognito, EC2, Route 53, S3, Google Ads API, Big Commerce, Dynamo DB, and JavaScript/TypeScript.

EDUCATION

University of Belgrade Master's Degree, Computer Science 2009 - 2013

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

Sotex Solutions | July 2016 - May 2018

- Implemented a responsive React website from scratch for a social media startup
- Built a React web app using hooks, Redux, best practices
- Constructed a REST and Socket API in Node.js (using the Express.js framework and Socket.IO library)
- Created an eCommerce website using NextJS and Contentful
- Built an eCommerce back-end using NestJS, integrated PostgreSQL and used TypeORM

FULL-STACK ENGINEER

Rare Crew | Feb 2014 - June 2016

- Designed and created a knowledge management platform on a knowledge graph, utilizing a range of technologies, including Node.js, Typescript, React, and Mobx
- Developed 2+ full-stack web applications to analyze and process data for different clients
- Optimized the company's complaint handling process by creating and delivering highly efficient app-based solutions
- Developed and implemented a standalone data extraction "agent" and main-application features for a financial product based on Laravel & Vue.js